24wrestling.com 2004-12-05

# 24Wrestling.com | Updated 24 Hours A Day - Pro Wrestling News, WWE, TNA, Indy, Babes, Media, Live Play By Play, Spoilers, Discussion, Editorials, Wrestler Photos, Women, Video Games, Wrestling Information & More!

---  
|   | 

|  Breaking News Updated 24 Hours A Day! | 

Today is Sunday, December 5th, 2004  
  
---|---  
  
| 

_Last Updated: 2/1/2004_

**Introduction**

> 24Wrestling.com wants to help you make the most of your visit to our web sites, and that includes helping to protect your personal privacy. Most of the features on our web sites are offered without collecting any Personal Information from you. You can surf 24Wrestling.com’s web sites and view much of our content anonymously. For those areas of our web sites and services that do require us to collect Personal Information, this Privacy Policy will tell you what you need to know to make good decisions for yourself and your family.
> 
> This Privacy Policy discloses when and how we collect, use, share, and safeguard information from this web site. The Personal Information we collect depends on what you do when you visit our sites or use the various products or services we offer. This Privacy Policy also explains what to do if you do not want to provide Personal Information when you visit our web sites, and how to correct or change information you have already provided to us.
> 
> By using this web site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use our web sites.
> 
> As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information, such as your name, street address, telephone number, date of birth and e-mail address. When Personal Information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form on the web site. When you make a purchase, or sign up for a paid service, a third party website (PayPal.com) handles credit card transactions. You can view PayPal's Privacy Policy by clicking [ here](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside).

**Children**

> 24Wrestling.com.com is committed to providing special protection for the privacy of children who may visit our web sites. 24Wrestling.com is also committed to fully complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We encourage parents to spend time online with their children, become familiar with the features of our web sites and participate in the activities offered on our web sites. Our protections for the privacy of children include the following:
> 
>   * We do not knowingly collect, use or retain any Personal Information, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes), from visitors to this web site who are age 12 or younger. In addition, we will delete any records of such Personal Information that come to our attention.
>   * Since we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from visitors to this web site who are age 12 or younger, we do not disclose or transfer any such information to third parties.
>   * We do not request any visitor to provide any information about their family members, friends or other persons.
>   * We do not allow visitors who are age 12 or younger to be listed in any directory of registered users, to participate in any of our chat services, to register for contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters, or to receive direct marketing from ProWrestlingFans.com or from our third-party affiliates or service or product providers. 
> 

**Special Note to Parents**

> If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information at one of our web sites, we invite you to notify us so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services (see Opt-Out below). We appreciate your cooperation in assisting us to provide a safe and enjoyable online experience for your children.

**Collection of Personal Information**

> 24Wrestling.com collects Personal Information from visitors to our web sites in the following ways:
> 
>   * Subscriptions to our newsletters.
>   * Participation in contests and sweepstakes.
>   * Registrations to receive free downloadable desktop applications (e.g., screensavers).
>   * Registrations to participate in chat services, message boards etc.
>   * Registrations to send electronic greeting cards.
>   * Purchases of merchandise (including subscriptions).
>   * E-mail transmitted via various links on our web sites.
> 

> 
> The use of any of these services is entirely optional and voluntary; however, if you do not provide the Personal Information requested, we may elect to not make the related services available for your use. If you send us an e-mail in which you disclose Personal Information, we will use it to discuss the subject of your correspondence and, if appropriate, share it with other interested parties (such as manufacturers of merchandise you have purchased from a web site).

**Cookies**

> In order to track your use of the site, "cookies" may be employed. Cookies are pieces of information that are sent by web sites and stored in your computer's hard drive, which provide you a service by allowing us to recognize your computer to save you from having to re-enter the same data every time you visit our web sites. They also allow us to learn how visitors use our web sites. This user data is aggregated for tracking purposes primarily by tallying pages viewed throughout our web sites and logging Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses and browser types.
> 
> Aggregated usage data enables us to tailor our content to our visitors’ interests and to help our advertisers better understand the preferences of our audience. Providing such usage data to advertisers is essential to keeping as many of our services free to visitors as is reasonably possible. This information does not reveal your identity although, in some cases, we may have to combine this non-identifiable information with Personal Information to enforce compliance with our Terms of Service or to protect our service, web sites, visitors or others.
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to the site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
> 
> If you do not want to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject them. However, if you turn cookies off, you will not have access to some 24Wrestling.com features and services.

**Visitors From Outside the United States**

> All Personal Information collected at our web sites is collected and stored in the United States. By submitting Personal Information to this web site, you are consenting to the storage of your Personal Information in the United States.

**How We Use Your Information**

> We limit the manner in which your Personal Information is used. We use Personal Information to provide you the products and services you want, to better understand and serve the needs of the 24Wrestling.com community, and to provide news and information to community members on new content, products and features of the web sites via direct e-mail. If you have registered with us and do not want to be contacted in the future by 24Wrestling.com.com or our advertising partners, please see Opt-Out below.
> 
> If you order a product or service from us or register for one of our contests, promotions, or interactive services, 24Wrestling.com may share Personal Information with service providers, suppliers and other third parties (for example, sweepstakes sponsors or delivery services) that assist us in operating the web sites or providing the products or services. When we share your Personal Information with third parties, they may use your Personal Information to send you information on their additional products or services, but 24Wrestling.com does not allow them to sell or transfer your Personal Information to others. We do not otherwise sell or provide your Personal Information to third parties.
> 
> Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order.

**Links to Third Party Web Sites**

> Please be advised that this web site contains certain hyperlinks to other web sites, some of which may display 24wrestling.com’s logos or other 24wrestling.com content. These web sites may have privacy policies; however, all of these web sites and their privacy policies are independent of our web sites or this Privacy Policy. 24wrestling.com is not responsible for compliance with other web sites’ privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing any Personal Information to these web sites.

**Third Party Ad Servers**

> The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by third party advertising companies, our Web advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, date/time at which the ads were shown, the advertisers' cookies, and IP address (but not your, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. In addition, we share web site usage information about visitors to our sites with these companies for the purposes of managing and targeting advertisements, measuring their effectiveness, and for market research analysis on our site and other sites. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising company may note some of the pages you visit on our site through the use of 1x1 pixel tags (also called clear gifs). For more information about ValueClick or cookies, please visit their website by clicking [here](http://www.valueclick.com/).

**Limitations on Use of Personal Information**

> We will only use or retain your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, and only for so long as is needed to fulfill your requests, support the services you have requested, process your orders, or comply with the law.

**Security of Personal Information**

> We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure, including the use of Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology to protect credit card information and other Personal Information you provide in connection with purchases, paid subscriptions or other similar transactions.

**Opt-Out**

> Any feature on our web sites requiring registration allows you to opt-out from receiving any newsletters, product offers, or other correspondence from either us or our business affiliates. In addition, if after registering, you would no longer like to receive any such materials or correspondence, send an e-mail by clicking [here](mailto:tim@w3bsite.com). Indicate your preference to “unsubscribe,” and we will promptly remove you from our list. Please be sure to include your name and e-mail address in the e-mail. You will need to send separate e-mails if you are registered for more than one of our features or services.
> 
> If you want to prevent a third party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt-out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third party advertising companies' privacy policies.
> 
> If you believe your child (age 12 or younger) has provided us with Personal Information and/or is receiving access to certain features or services, including marketing communications, we invite you to notify us via e-mail by clicking [here](mailto:kevin@el3int.com). We will delete this Personal Information and/or discontinue your child’s access to the related features or services.

**Changes in This Privacy Policy**

> 24wrestling.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here and we will change the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

---|---
